Stan Davis

Games Programmer

Email: stanley.samson.davis@gmail.com

Portfolio: standavis.dev

PROFILE

I am an enthusiastic and creatively driven programmer with over 3 years experience in games development. This has provided me an extensive knowledge of various languages and game engines including C++, C#, Unity, and Unreal. I have a keen interest in building various gameplay systems, and I am constantly learning new skills through personal development. Check out my portfolio for selection of my previous and current projects.

SKILLS

Languages	Game Engines / APIs	Other Skills
C++	Unity Engine	Git
C#	Unreal Engine 4	Collaboration (Slack/JIRA/Teams/Zoom)
LUA	DirectX	Web (HTML / CSS / JavaScript)
HLSL	SDL2	Video Editing (Premiere Pro)
Swift / SwiftUI Rust	Godot Engine	Music Production / Sound Design (Ableton Live / FL Studio / VST Plugins)

WORK HISTORY

Tesco Colleague (2022 - Present) Stocking products and customer service.

Honest Burgers (2021 - 2022) Serving food, drinks, taking payments, and providing customer service.

The Berkeley - Wetherspoons (2018 - 2019) Serving drinks, taking payments, and customer service.

Early Career (2015-2017)

Feel free to ask for further details.

EDUCATION

Games Technology BSc (Hons) (2019 - 2022) University of the West of England Grade: **2:1**

BTEC Extended Diploma in Music Technology

Phone: 07503834590

Level 3 (2015-2017) Truro College Grade: **DMM**

9 GCSEs (inc. Maths & English) (2012-2015)

Poltair School Grade: **B-C**

HOBBIES & INTERESTS

Gaming, Game Design, Programming, Music Production, Sound Design, Building Lego